const quizSubjects = [
  {
    id: 1,
    title: "Maths",
  },
  {
    id: 2,
    title: "Indian History",
  },
  {
    id: 3,
    title: "General Knowledge",
  },
  {
    id: 4,
    title: "Geography",
  },
];

const quizSubCategory = [
  {
    id: 1,
    subjectId: 1,
    title: "Algebra",
  },
  {
    id: 2,
    subjectId: 1,
    title: "Geometry",
  },
  {
    id: 3,
    subjectId: 3,
    title: "Bollywood",
  },
  {
    id: 4,
    subjectId: 3,
    title: "Culture",
  },
  {
    id: 5,
    subjectId: 4,
    title: "Indian Geography",
  },
  {
    id: 6,
    subjectId: 4,
    title: "World Geography",
  },
];

const quizeQuestions = [
  {
    id: 1,
    subCategoryId: 1,
    question: "What is three fifth of 100?",
    optionA: "3",
    optionB: "5",
    optionC: "20",
    optionD: "60",
    correctAnswer: "60",
  },
  {
    id: 2,
    subCategoryId: 1,
    question: "What is the remainder of 21 divided by 7?",
    optionA: "21",
    optionB: "7",
    optionC: "1",
    optionD: "None of these",
    correctAnswer: "None of these",
  },
  {
    id: 3,
    subCategoryId: 1,
    question: "What is 7% equal to?",
    optionA: "7",
    optionB: "0.07",
    optionC: "0.007",
    optionD: "0.0007",
    correctAnswer: "0.07",
  },
  {
    id: 4,
    subCategoryId: 2,
    question: "What does not extend and has end points?",
    optionA: "line segment",
    optionB: "ray",
    optionC: "angle",
    optionD: "None of these",
    correctAnswer: "line segment",
  },
  {
    id: 5,
    subCategoryId: 2,
    question: "What is an angle with 90 degrees called?",
    optionA: "right angle",
    optionB: "obtuse angle",
    optionC: "acute angle",
    optionD: "None of these",
    correctAnswer: "right angle",
  },
  {
    id: 6,
    subCategoryId: 2,
    question: "Which one is the 3-D shape in given shapes?",
    optionA: "square",
    optionB: "rectangle",
    optionC: "circle",
    optionD: "cuboid",
    correctAnswer: "cuboid",
  },
  {
    id: 7,
    subCategoryId: 3,
    question: "Who was known as the King of Bollywood Music?",
    optionA: "Kishor Kumar",
    optionB: "Shahrukh Khan",
    optionC: "Amir Khan",
    optionD: "Shaan",
    correctAnswer: "Kishor Kumar",
  },
  {
    id: 8,
    subCategoryId: 3,
    question: "What movie genre does “Hungama” belong to?",
    optionA: "Comedy",
    optionB: "Action",
    optionC: "Thriller",
    optionD: "Horror",
    correctAnswer: "Comedy",
  },
  {
    id: 9,
    subCategoryId: 3,
    question:
      "How many Best Actor awards have Filmfare Dilip Kumar and Shahrukh won in the Filmfare?",
    optionA: "6",
    optionB: "9",
    optionC: "10",
    optionD: "5",
    correctAnswer: "10",
  },
  {
    id: 10,
    subCategoryId: 4,
    question: "The ratio of width of our National flag to its length is?",
    optionA: "2:3",
    optionB: "2:4",
    optionC: "5:6",
    optionD: "4:5",
    correctAnswer: "2:3",
  },
  {
    id: 11,
    subCategoryId: 4,
    question:
      "'Natya - Shastra' the main source of India's classical dances was written by?",
    optionA: "Narad Muni",
    optionB: "Bharat Muni",
    optionC: "Abhinav Gupta",
    optionD: "Vidhya Kumar",
    correctAnswer: "Bharat Muni",
  },
  {
    id: 12,
    subCategoryId: 4,
    question: "'Dandia' is a popular dance of?",
    optionA: "Gujrat",
    optionB: "Haryana",
    optionC: "Tamil Nadu",
    optionD: "Maharashtra",
    correctAnswer: "Gujrat",
  },
  {
    id: 13,
    subCategoryId: 4,
    question:
      "Which of the following folk dance forms is associated with Gujarat?",
    optionA: "Bharatnatyam",
    optionB: "Garba",
    optionC: "Disco",
    optionD: "Salsa",
    correctAnswer: "Garba",
  },
  {
    id: 14,
    subCategoryId: 4,
    question:
      "The Rath Yatra at Puri is celebrated in honour of which Hindu deity?",
    optionA: "Ram",
    optionB: "Krishna",
    optionC: "Jaganath",
    optionD: "Shiva",
    correctAnswer: "Jaganath",
  },
  {
    id: 15,
    subCategoryId: 5,
    question: "The only state in India that produces saffron is?",
    optionA: "Jammu & Kashmir",
    optionB: "Madhya Pradesh",
    optionC: "Maharashtra",
    optionD: "Punjab",
    correctAnswer: "Jammu & Kashmir",
  },
  {
    id: 16,
    subCategoryId: 5,
    question: "The percentage of irrigated land in India is about?",
    optionA: "75%",
    optionB: "45%",
    optionC: "90%",
    optionD: "35%",
    correctAnswer: "35%",
  },
  {
    id: 17,
    subCategoryId: 5,
    question: "The India's highest annual rainfall is reported at?",
    optionA: "Namchi, Sikkim",
    optionB: "Churu, Rajasthan",
    optionC: "Mawsynram, Meghalaya",
    optionD: "Chamba, Himachal Pradesh",
    correctAnswer: "Mawsynram, Meghalaya",
  },
  {
    id: 18,
    subCategoryId: 5,
    question: "The zonal soil type of peninsular India belongs to?",
    optionA: "Yellow Soils",
    optionB: "Black soils",
    optionC: "Red soils",
    optionD: "Older alluvium",
    correctAnswer: "Red soils",
  },
  {
    id: 19,
    subCategoryId: 5,
    question:
      "Which of the following food grain crops occupies the largest part of the cropped area in India?",
    optionA: "Barley and maize",
    optionB: "Jowar & Bajra",
    optionC: "Rice",
    optionD: "Wheat",
    correctAnswer: "Rice",
  },
  {
    id: 20,
    subCategoryId: 6,
    question: "The hazards of radiation belts include?",
    optionA: "deterioration of electronic circuits",
    optionB: "damage of solar cells of spacecraft",
    optionC: "adverse effect on living organisms",
    optionD: "All of the above",
    correctAnswer: "All of the above",
  },
  {
    id: 21,
    subCategoryId: 6,
    question: "The great Victoria Desert is located in?",
    optionA: "Australia",
    optionB: "Canada",
    optionC: "North America",
    optionD: "West Africa",
    correctAnswer: "Australia",
  },
  {
    id: 22,
    subCategoryId: 6,
    question: "The intersecting lines drawn on maps and globes are?",
    optionA: "latitudes",
    optionB: "longitudes",
    optionC: "equator",
    optionD: "geographic grids",
    correctAnswer: "geographic grids",
  },
  {
    id: 23,
    subCategoryId: 6,
    question: "The humidity of the air depends upon?",
    optionA: "temperature",
    optionB: "location",
    optionC: "weather",
    optionD: "all of the above",
    correctAnswer: "all of the above",
  },
  {
    id: 24,
    subCategoryId: 6,
    question: "The largest glaciers are?",
    optionA: "mountain glaciers",
    optionB: "alpine glaciers",
    optionC: "continental glaciers",
    optionD: "piedmont glaciers",
    correctAnswer: "continental glaciers",
  },
  {
    id: 25,
    subCategoryId: 1,
    question: "Today is Monday. After 61 days, it will be?",
    optionA: "Tuesday",
    optionB: "Wednesday",
    optionC: "Saturday",
    optionD: "Thursday",
    correctAnswer: "Saturday",
  },
  {
    id: 26,
    subCategoryId: 1,
    question: "The last day of a century cannot be?",
    optionA: "Monday",
    optionB: "Wednesday",
    optionC: "Tuesday",
    optionD: "Friday",
    correctAnswer: "Tuesday",
  },
  {
    id: 27,
    subCategoryId: 2,
    question: "What is the shape with eight sides called?",
    optionA: "octagon",
    optionB: "rectangle",
    optionC: "hexagon",
    optionD: "star",
    correctAnswer: "octagon",
  },
  {
    id: 28,
    subCategoryId: 2,
    question: "How many sides does a circle have?",
    optionA: "0",
    optionB: "1",
    optionC: "4",
    optionD: "5",
    correctAnswer: "0",
  },
  {
    id: 29,
    subCategoryId: 3,
    question:
      "Which singer is often considered to be the Father of Hindi movie singing?",
    optionA: "Arijit Singh",
    optionB: "Kumar Sanu",
    optionC: "Kundanlal Saigal",
    optionD: "None of these",
    correctAnswer: "Kundanlal Saigal",
  },
  {
    id: 30,
    subCategoryId: 3,
    question: "In which movie did Preity Zinta make her debut?",
    optionA: "Kya Kehna",
    optionB: "Soldier",
    optionC: "Dil se",
    optionD: "None of these",
    correctAnswer: "Dil se",
  },
];

export { quizSubjects, quizSubCategory };
